ehomeinsurance.co.uk 2013-10-06

# eHome Home Insurance

## Privacy And Security

## 1\. Introduction 

eHome Insurance are committed to both respecting your privacy and providing a secure website so your personal information is protected. You can be assured any information you provide to us will be used strictly in accordance with the terms laid out in this statement.

## 2\. Collecting Information

We will only look to request necessary information from you and will only use and disclose this information in the course of arranging and administering your insurance, and to inform you of other services which we feel maybe appropriate to you. The type of information we will collect will include, for example, your name and postal address, date of birth, telephone number, email address, credit/debit card details and bank account details. The information we hold will be, to the best of our knowledge, accurate and up to date. Under the Data Protection Act you have the right to see the personal information that we hold about you in our records. All personal information is treated confidentially and is safely stored on our computer, with security systems preventing unauthorised access.

## 3\. Confidentiality

We will endeavour to treat all your personal information as private and confidential. Other than under the terms of this privacy statement we will not disclose any of your information to anyone. We would like to bring your attention to our obligations to disclose information in the following exceptional cases permitted by law. These are:

  * Where we are legally forced to
  * Where there is a duty to the public to disclose information
  * Where you have given permission to disclose information
  * Where we have to protect our interest

## 4\. Information Security

How we protect your personal information from misuse and abuse is of great importance to us. We are constantly reviewing and enhancing our technical and physical security procedures to protect your personal data from unauthorised access.

You will only be able to access your policy by inputting your unique policy number and your email address. The eHome Insurance site also uses 128-bit secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology to encrypt sensitive information such as your financial information. When you request a quote from us, we will process the data on a secure server.

## 5\. How Your Information Will Be Used

Your information will be used for a number of purposes which include automatically processing your quotation, managing and administering your policy, claims handling and responding to complaints or policy enquiries. eHome Insurance and carefully selected third parties may use your information to keep you informed by post, telephone or email of products or services which maybe of interest to you. We will also contact you to remind you your insurance is due for renewal.

## 6\. Access To Your Information

You can write to us at any time to obtain details of the information we hold about you. Please write to:

     Data Protection Officer
     eHome Insurance
     Petitor House
     Riviera Park
     Nicholson Road
     Torquay
     TQ2 7TD

Please quote your name, postal address and email address along with the details of your requirement. We will take reasonable steps to confirm your identity before providing you with details of any personal information we may hold about you. Therefore we would be grateful if you could provide two forms of identification such as a copy of a passport or driving licence and a copy of a utility bill to confirm address. In accordance with the Data Protection Act, 1998 we are entitled to charge £10 to cover the administration costs involved with this process.

## 7\. Cookies

Our web site use a number of different cookies. Here we explain the different type of cookies we use and why we use them.

#### What is a cookie?

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by websites or sometimes by emails. They provide useful information to companies, which helps in all sorts of ways. For you, it means you can use our site more efficiently and save you time by not having to re-enter your details each time you visit. They also make sure you receive the most relevant information from us.

There are two main categories of cookies:

  * Persistent cookies - These cookies stay your computer until they are removed manually or automatically 
  * Session cookies - These cookies remain on your computer until you close your browser when they are automatically deleted. 

### Cookies we use and why we use them

#### Essential cookies

Essential cookies are technical cookies that are required for the operation of our sites. Without essential cookies our web site can't operate properly. Essential cookies include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas. 

#### Performance cookies

Performance cookies allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors to our web site and to see how visitors move around them. This helps us to improve the way our web site works by enabling us to tailor our site to the way visitors use them. The information we collect from performance cookies is aggregated which means that we cannot identify you from it. 

#### Your right to refuse cookies and what happens if you refuse them

You can refuse cookies by activating the relevant setting on your browser. However, if you do so you may not be able to access all or parts of our sites. If you carry on using our sites and do not change your browser settings we will assume you consent to us using cookies as described above.
